kwiziq.com 2014-09-07

# Privacy Policy

We recognize that privacy is important. 

This Privacy Policy applies to all of the products, services and websites offered by Kwiziq (Kwiziq Ltd) **including French-test.com**. If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us through our website.

Information we collect and how we use it:  
We offer a number of services that do not require you to register for an account or provide any personal information to us, such as our Historical Word of the Day, games like Match Mania (whilst not logged in to our site) and our Twitter Language Bites service. In order to provide our full range of services, we may collect the following types of information:

  * Information you provide - When you sign up for a Kwiziq Account or other Kwiziq service or promotion that requires registration, we ask you for personal information (such as your name, email address and an account password; we store your password in an encrypted form so that even we do not know it.)
  * Financial information - If we need to take credit card, financial or payment details from you, we will either use a regulated third party (such as PayPal, Google Checkout, or a service provided by a regulated bank) in which case they may store your financial details, or we will store data in an encrypted form. We will never store financial information you supply to us in a form which is not secure.
  * Your public profile - We may provide the ability for you to create a public profile, including personal details and one more photos of yourself. Your profile may also be linked to your Facebook account in which case some data may be shared with Facebook. You may need to adjust your Facebook privacy settings. Anything you write about yourself in the details section of your profile is publicly available and may be available for other users to see and you should not post anything you wish to keep private here. Do not write contact details such as your email address on your profile except in the contact details fields which are private and remain unpublished unless you explicitly give permission to certain users to see them.
  * Cookies - When you visit our website we send one or more cookies - a small file containing a string of characters - to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including for storing user preferences. We do not currently, but Kwiziq may in the future use cookies to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads on our site to ensure their relevance to you.
  * Log information - When you access Kwiziq services, our servers automatically record information that your browser sends whenever you visit sections of our website. These server logs may include information such as your web request, Internet Protocol address, browser type, browser language, the date and time of your request and one or more cookies that may uniquely identify your browser.
  * Other Data We may store about you  
We may collect data about your language knowledge based on your use of our services, tools and games in order to support your language learning and tailor our educational programmes to your specific needs. We retain the right to this data, but we collect it for your benefit. You can see the data we hold about you and your language skills using the various reports available on the site. You may also request to see all the data we hold about you and we will do our best to provide it directly (though we cannot guarantee to supply it in a particular form).
  * User communications - When you send email or other communications to Kwiziq, we may retain those communications in order to process your inquiries, respond to your requests and improve our services.
  * Links - Kwiziq may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our services, customized content and advertising.

Kwiziq only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy and/or the supplementary privacy notices for specific services. In addition to the above, such purposes include:

  * Providing our services, including the display of customized content and advertising;
  * Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services;
  * Ensuring the technical functioning of our services;
  * Protecting the rights or property of Kwiziq or our users; and  
Developing new services.

###  Cookies

Kwiziq utilises "cookies". A cookie is a piece of data stored on the user's hard drive containing information about the user. Kwiziq uses cookies to keep track of how often you visit our site, previous purchases and to deliver content specific to your interests. Most browsers are automatically set to accept cookies but you can alter the settings of your browser to prevent automatic acceptance - a good guide for all browsers is [here](http://www.lavasoft.com/mylavasoft/securitycenter/blog/configure-your-browser-to-deal-with-cookies). If you choose not to receive cookies, you may still use most of the features of our website, including the ability to purchase items. For more information on cookies and how to disable them, you can consult the information provided by the Interactive Advertising Bureau at [www.allaboutcookies.org](http://www.allaboutcookies.org/)

###  Use of cookies

Cookies are small text files that are placed on your computer by websites that you visit. They are widely used in order to make websites work, or work more efficiently, as well as to provide information to the owners of the site.

The table below explains the cookies we use and why.

**Cookie** |  **Name** |  **Purpose** |  **More information**  
---|---|---|---  
**Google Analytics** |  _utma |  These cookies are used to collect information about how visitors use our site. We use the information to compile reports and to help us improve the site. The cookies collect information in an anonymous form, including the number of visitors to the site, where visitors have come to the site from and the pages they visited. |  [Google Privacy](http://www.google.co.uk/intl/en/analytics/privacyoverview.html "External link")  
_utmb  
_utmc  
_utmz  
**CMS cookie** |  PHPSESSID |  This is a cookie set by our content management system to manage  |     
**Facebook link** |  fbsr_158322574190167 |  A cookie set by our Facebook plugin which allows users who have chosen to log in with facebook to do so.  This has no effect without your explicit permission to act in this way. |     
  
In addition to those above some of our "share" functions such as Facebook Like or Tweet set cookies for their own purposes.  These can vary and are not set explicitly by kwiziq.com - these too can be blocked by configuring your browser settings. 

Kwiziq processes personal information on our servers in the United States of America, United Kingdom, and in other countries. In some cases, we process personal information on a server outside your own country. We may process personal information to provide our own services. In some cases, we may process personal information on behalf of and according to the instructions of a third party, such as our advertising partners.

####  Choices for personal information

When you sign up for a particular service that requires registration, we may ask you to provide additional personal information. If we use this information in a manner different than the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use.

If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent.

Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some Kwiziq features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled.

Kwiziq may uses 3rd party advertising cookies such as Google's AdSense

You can decline to submit personal information to any of our services, in which case Kwiziq may not be able to provide those services to you.

####  Information sharing

Kwiziq only shares personal information with other companies or individuals outside of Kwiziq in the following limited circumstances:

The data we store about your language skills may be made available to 3rd party language services that use our API in order that they can provide services to help you improve your language skills but they may not store this data about you. For example, a 3rd party may have written a game that helps improve vocabulary skills that, using our API, can work out what vocabulary you need to practice next in order to improve and then serve the content most suited to your needs.

We require opt-in consent for the sharing of any sensitive personal information.

We provide such information to our subsidiaries, affiliated companies or other trusted businesses or persons for the purpose of processing personal information on our behalf. We require that these parties agree to process such information based on our instructions and in compliance with this Privacy Policy and any other appropriate confidentiality and security measures.  
We have a good faith belief that access, use, preservation or disclosure of such information is reasonably necessary to (a) satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable governmental request, (b) enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof, (c) detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues, or (d) protect against harm to the rights, property or safety of Kwiziq, its users or the public as required or permitted by law.  
If Kwiziq becomes involved in a merger, acquisition, or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, we will ensure the confidentiality of any personal information involved in such transactions and provide notice before personal information is transferred and becomes subject to a different privacy policy.

We may share with third parties certain pieces of aggregated, non-personal information, such as the number of users who searched for a particular term, for example, or how many users reached a certain level of competence in a language. Such information does not identify you individually.

Please contact us using our website for any additional questions about the management or use of personal data.

####  Information security

We take appropriate security measures to protect against unauthorized access to or unauthorized alteration, disclosure or destruction of data. These include internal reviews of our data collection, storage and processing practices and security measures, as well as physical security measures to guard against unauthorized access to systems where we store personal data.

We restrict access to personal information to Kwiziq employees, contractors and agents who need to know that information in order to operate, develop or improve our services. These individuals are bound by confidentiality obligations and may be subject to discipline, including termination and criminal prosecution, if they fail to meet these obligations.

####  Data integrity

Kwiziq processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information we process is accurate, complete, and current, but we depend on our users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary.

####  Accessing, updating or deleting personal information

If you no longer wish us to hold data about you, then you can request us to purge your account and we will destroy any data we hold that could be used to identify you. We reserve the right to keep statistical or anonymised data. We will no longer have any way of knowing to whom the data once referred.

When you use Kwiziq services, we make good faith efforts to provide you with access to your personal information and either to correct this data if it is inaccurate or to delete such data at your request if it is not otherwise required to be retained by law or for legitimate business purposes. We ask individual users to identify themselves and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed before processing such requests, and we may decline to process requests that are unreasonably repetitive or systematic, require disproportionate technical effort, jeopardize the privacy of others, or would be extremely impractical (for instance, requests concerning information residing on backup tapes), or for which access is not otherwise required. In any case where we provide information access and correction, we perform this service free of charge, except if doing so would require a disproportionate effort. Some of our services have different procedures to access, correct or delete users' personal information. We provide the details for these procedures in the specific privacy notices or FAQs for these services.

####  Changes to this Privacy Policy

Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent, and we expect most such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on this page and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). Each version of this Privacy Policy will be identified at the top of the page by its effective date, and we will also keep prior versions of this Privacy Policy in an archive for your review.

If you have any additional questions or concerns about this Privacy Policy, please feel free to contact us any time through this website.
